Subtitles by explosiveskull Resync by GoldenBeard
COACH 1 : Nice , easy mile now , warm it up !
- COACH 2 : Take your time . - COACH 3 : Hurry up !
- ( WHISTLE BLOWS ) - Aww .
It 'd be so much cuter if you were wearing little shoes .
It 'd be cuter if he exploded at the end .
( MEOWING )
( SNEEZES )
- Excuse me . - Bless you .
- You know ... - Black lung .
Did you know that pilgrims used to think sneezing
meant you were expelling demons ?
- What ? - ( LAUGHS ) That 's why I never sneeze .
I want to keep them all
- in my soul . - Your soul .
If I had one .
WREN : Twitter poll .
If you could stay one age forever , what would it be ?
- Easy . 21 . - No way . I 'd be 10 .
Oh , no , 10 was the worst , man .
I say , 30 . It 's like the height of sophistication .
- You ? - What about the age we are right now ?
I 'd like to stay like this forever .
Seriously ? I mean , what 's wrong with you ?
Okay , fine . The age we are right now ,
but we could all live in a house together .
Okay , fine . But without Wren , though ?
Yeah , obviously , that goes without saying .
Super funny . Like , whoa .
WREN : ( IN AUSTRALIAN ACCENT ) Guys , the dudebros in their natural habitat .
Let 's observe , shall we ?
( IN NORMAL VOICE ) Hey , Tom ! So , what 's the plan tonight ?
- Big plans ... - Hey .
- It 's top secret . - Oh , I see . A circle jerk ?
( GIRLS LAUGH )
- Hey , Chloe . - Hey , Kyle .
So , what 's the big secret ?
I mean , I could tell you ,
- but then , I 'd have to kill you . - ( LAUGHS )
- Okay , buddy . - Yeah .
Yeah . It 's very intriguing .
You guys , I got to go get my sister , but I love you . Bye .
WREN : See you later . I 'll pick you up tonight .
- I 'm sorry . - Bye . It 's okay .
( SCHOOL BELL RINGING )
Bumped into Coach Sanders today .
Said your 1,600-meter time is really improving .
All that training 's paying off .
Nice work , sweetheart .
Did you tell them Delores Constantino quit the team ?
Why ?
She 's pregnant .
What is she planning to do , now ?
She 's gonna drop out , and keep the baby .
I assume Wren is gonna be at Katie 's tonight ?
Yeah . So ?
So , what are you guys gonna do ?
You know , drink a lot of vodka , and meet guys online .
Funny . Very funny .
- Can I come ? - Not a chance .
- You said I could come next time . - I lied .
( DOORBELL RINGING )
- Hey . - Hey .
Do you think I could hang out with you guys ?
Uh , yeah , not tonight , grasshopper .
Sorry . Maybe next time .
Oh , I wore the shirt you gave me to school .
Got sent to the principal 's office .
- Well done , man . Yes . - Hey .
- WREN : Hey . - Goodbye .
Bye .
Love me .
Bye , Lizzie .
( KNOCKING ON DOOR )
- Hey . - Hey .
( WHISPERING ) Don 't make any noise . It 's dormant .
Just another exciting Friday night at the Jensens .
- ( GIRLS LAUGHING ) - WREN : No ? Oh ?
Yeah , it 's girl gaze porn .
- ( POP MUSIC PLAYING ) - You know how they have POV porn ?
- Yeah . - This one 's from our perspective .
- I don 't want to see that . - KATIE : For sure .
- ( LAUGHING ) - Oh , my God .
Do you think she likes that ?
- Oh , my God ! - No !
Oh , God ! Once you see it , you just can 't unsee it .
( GIRLS LAUGHING )
- ( SIGHS ) - ( FOOTFALLS OVERHEAD )
( OBJECTS CLATTERING )
What the hell is he doing ?
He 's probably just looking for another bottle .
- Sometimes , I wish I could just leave . - WREN : I know .
Why don 't we just all leave ? Get out of this stupid town together .
Where would we go ?
I have friends in Paris . We could totally stay with them .
What friends ? You 've never been to Paris .
- My mom has friends there , idiot . - Don 't I wish .
I 'll just be stuck here forever , in this shithole .
( HALLIE GROANS )
- ( GIRLS LAUGHING ) - ( THUDDING OVERHEAD )
WREN : Seriously ! No , I think you and Carl would make an adorable couple .
It 's " Kyle , " and I don 't like him .
Yeah , yeah , yeah . Whatever , you know .
But we all know that you wish you were
at their little secret sausage fest right now .
No .
But I do know what their secret is .
WREN : Oh , yeah ? Do tell .
So , they 're getting together tonight at Tom 's house
in his garage , to summon Slender Man .
- Creepy . - Who 's Slender Man ?
Yeah , he 's the guy who makes all those kids disappear .
Why have I not heard of this ?
That 's a much longer conversation .
- Listen . - Troll ...
" Slender Man can manifest in a variety of forms .
" Certain accounts speak of a hypnotic power
" that renders his victims helpless to stop themselves
" from walking into waiting arms .
" While his origins and motives are completely unknown ,
" he preys upon innocent youth .
" Once you see him , you 're his .
" Some he takes , some he doesn 't .
" Nobody knows why he takes who he takes , or why he leaves who he leaves .
" But the ones he leaves behind are messed up forever . "
All right , here it is . " How to summon Slender Man . "
- Guys , we so have to do this . - CHLOE : We actually don 't .
Actually .
If they 're doing it , we 're doing it .
KATIE : This feels wrong . This feels like
Russian malware-y virus-type shit .
Come on , don 't be such a wuss .
" Those who hear the three bells toll
" accept his invitation .
" When you hear the first , you must close your eyes ,
" keeping words unspoken .
" If one wants to hear , you must listen closely ,
" for they are soft and distant .
" With eyes still closed and mind wide open ,
" clear your thoughts and await the second ,
" opening your eyes only once you 've heard the third . "
WREN : Hmm .
( TREES CREAKING )
( GIRLS GASPING )
( BELL TOLLS )
Are you serious ? This is ...
ALL : Shh !
( BELL TOLLS )
( CREAKING )
What a stupid video . Honestly .
( KATIE LAUGHS )
( NERVOUS LAUGHING )
( SIGHS ) Can we do something else ?
- Let 's watch a movie . - Yeah .
( DOG BARKING IN DISTANCE )
( OBJECTS CLATTERING )
( FOOTFALLS OVERHEAD )
( WIND HOWLING )
( THUNDER CRASHES )
( GASPS )
( CHURCH BELLS TOLLING )
TOUR GUIDE : This burial ground dates back
all the way to the Revolutionary War ,
which was 1775 to 1783 .
In 2004 , it was put on the National Registry of Historical Sites ,
which was very exciting .
Initially , all of this land belonged to Thomas Clifton ,
who left it to the town of Winsford in his will in 1674 .
( CRACKLING )
You guys , I threw up twice this morning , before I got on the bus .
( GASPS ) Is it Carl 's ?
Ha . That 's hilarious , and also , scientifically impossible .
Have you been having nightmares ?
Mmm-mmm .
Have you ?
Uh ...
About what ?
( SCOFFS ) It 's nothing , really . It 's just that video .
TOUR GUIDE : ... stronger and more durable , which is also ...
Hey , Katie ?
Katie , are you okay ?
Yes .
( WIND HOWLING )
( CREAKING )
( INAUDIBLE )
Katie ? Cut this shit out , man .
All right , we 're all prisoners because of you .
So , none of you saw where she went ?
- No . - Really ?
- Damn it . - I mean , where is she ?
Yeah , she still hasn 't answered any of my texts .
( SIREN WAILING )
GIRL : Why are the police here ?
Oh , shit .
TOM : You see her ?
HALLIE : Mmm-mmm .
( ENGINE STARTING )
- ( DOG BARKING ) - ( POLICE RADIO CHATTER )
NEWS ANCHOR : ( ON TABLET ) Teenager Katie Jensen was last seen on Wednesday ,
during a school field trip to the historic Clifton Cemetery .
As of now , local police have no leads ,
but are questioning friends and family members
in hopes of gaining insight into the reason for her disappearance .
Citizens with any information are being urged to contact local authorities .
You should tell me what really happened to Katie .
We never keep secrets from each other .
How would you know ? You don 't know that . Do your homework .
Come on , I don 't want to talk about it .
It was a boy , right ? You think I 'll tell ? I 'd never tell .
You 'd totally tell .
Not Mom and Dad .
Totally Mom and Dad .
Maybe .
Definitely , but you get points for honesty .
So , tell me .
You don 't know . Do you ?
Just do your work , Lizzie .
- Hallie . - Lizzie .
Fine .
I could stay home alone , you know . I 'm old enough .
Physical age , maybe .
( DOOR OPENING )
Did you hear that ?
Hey , Mom ? Dad !
Hey , Mom ?
( DOOR SLAMS )
- Hallie , someone 's in here . - ( SHUSHING )
Stay here . Okay ? Don 't move .
( OBJECTS CLATTERING )
- ( DOG BARKING ) - ( GASPS )
( GASPING )
Hallie ? Hallie , what is it ? Hallie ...
- ( SHUSHING ) - ( WHIMPERING )
( DOOR RATTLING )
We called the police !
( RATTLING CONTINUES )
( POUNDING ON DOOR )
( DOORKNOB RATTLING )
MAN : Katie ? Katie ?
OFFICER : ( ON PHONE ) Police emergency . Can I help you ?
MAN : Katie .
( CELL PHONE BEEPS )
Katie , you here ?
( MAN CRYING )
Mr. Jensen ?
Where 's my daughter ?
I don 't know .
- Is Katie here ? Are you hiding her ? - No .
I don 't know where she is .
It 's all your fault .
She was never into this stuff .
- All this occult stuff . - Hallie ?
Lizzie , stay back .
- Where is she ? - I don 't know .
- Where is she ? - No ! Don 't ! Hallie !
- Where is my daughter ? - Hallie !
- Lizzie ! - Where is she ?
( HALLIE AND LIZZIE SCREAM )
Let 's go .
( LIZZIE SOBBING )
- Stay the hell away from my family ! - Hey , hey , hey !
HALLIE 'S DAD : You hear me , Jensen ?
( INAUDIBLE )
Did you guys really try and summon Slender Man ?
Why ?
We chickened out .
( BELL RINGING )
You chickened out .
- I chickened out ? - You chickened out .
- I remember you being the one ... - He chickened out .
... that chickened out .
Katie 's father broke into my house last night .
- What ? - What ?
He said something about Katie being into the occult ,
and then he blamed us for getting her into it .
Wait , what did he mean about Katie being into the occult ?
I don 't know . He was so wasted .
This could be the next wrinkle in the story .
I don 't want to play this game .
It 's not a game . Katie 's missing .
Yeah , and we know things that nobody else knows .
What do we know ?
We know that she watched that video .
Look , we all watched that video . It didn 't do anything .
When are we gonna admit that Katie was kidnapped ?
Somebody has her .
Yeah , but when we watched that video , it affected all of us .
Something happened . I felt it .
- I didn 't see anything . - I didn 't see anything , either .
Didn 't say I saw it . I said I felt it .
And I think you did , too .
And I 'm damn sure that Katie felt it ,
and that 's why she disappeared !
This is a bad idea .
It 's just a quick look around , okay ?
Plus , you know what , he 's probably totally passed out by now .
I don 't know , I just feel like there 's got to be something .
- You know , like a clue , maybe , or ... - You 're crazy .
You don 't realize how he was last night .
CHLOE : The back door is always unlocked for when Katie gets home late .
Just saying .
Great . Then let 's go .
Told ya .
( SNORING )
( DOORBELL RINGS )
Wren ?
Hi . Hi , Mr. Jensen .
What are you doing here ?
Well , I just wanted to come down
and see if there was anything that I could do , if I could help
in any way ?
Anything I could do .
I miss her .
People just don 't disappear .
You want to come in ?
That 'd be great .
She 's really gone .
The police must have taken her laptop .
HALLIE : What is all this ?
( WHISPERING ) She used to keep cigarettes and stuff in here .
Let 's just take it .
( TYPING )
HALLIE : Okay . Here 's the last site she visited .
What am I looking at ?
HALLIE : Here , click it .
Okay .
( CHILDREN GIGGLING )
( GIGGLES ECHOING )
Oh , shit .
All these , like , town names , and dates and stuff .
Click another one .
BOY 1 : Okay , guys . Let 's go .
I am Slender Man .
- BOY 1 : Dude . ( SHUSHING ) - BOY 2 : Guys , guys .
BOY 1 : Whoa , whoa . What is that ? What is that ?
I 'm so scared . I 'm so ...
( PANTING )
BOY 1 : Go , go , go !
- BOY 2 : Oh , God ! - BOY 1 : Dude , he 's there !
- I can 't ... - ( SCREAMING )
- It 's him . - I don 't like this .
- Wait , look . - What ?
AleeyKat93 .
Jeez .
They went back and forth , like , a gazillion times .
" I knew he was there before I saw him . "
It 's like they 're comparing experiences .
Wait , look . Katie posted a video .
HALLIE : Look , it 's from the night before she disappeared .
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( GASPING )
- What was that ? - What did you see ?
What did you see ?
- I don 't know , I ... - I don 't know , either .
- WREN : I talked to her . - HALLIE : Who ?
AleeyKat93 .
It was that girl that Katie was talking to on that website .
I messaged her , and she replied .
You went back on that website ?
She told me everything . He gets in your head like a virus .
What kind of virus ?
Like a computer virus that infects your hard drive ,
but instead of your hard drive , it 's your brain .
- Wren , you 're gonna need to slow down ... - No , listen to me .
Once the virus takes hold , he 's got you . It 's done .
Some he haunts , some he drives mad .
- And others , he takes , like ... - Like what ?
Katie .
Listen , I know that this ...
This is gonna sound crazy ,
but AleeyKat said we can
" unveil ourselves . "
Okay , if we just surrender something to him
that has personal meaning , something that we truly love .
What the hell does that mean ?
We can contact Slender Man .
Why would we do that ?
To get Katie back . Hello ?
Katie did it , and the next day , she was just gone .
Okay , Katie asked Slender Man
- to take her ? - Yes .
Why would she do that ?
I don 't know . You know , maybe she had an alcoholic father ,
and maybe she hated her life , and maybe she talked about
running away all the time , you know ?
Guys , the police have no leads .
Right ? Right ?
So , even if the odds are a million-to-one
that any of this is real , or that ...
That he has anything to do with Katie 's disappearance ,
we owe it to her to try .
WREN : This should work .
I guess that I 'll ...
Go first , then .
I ... ( CHUCKLES )
I made this in pottery class , when I was five .
This is a picture of me and my dad .
It 's the only one I have where we 're together .
It was taken a few months before he died .
My grandma made this when Lizzie was born .
She died eight years ago .
( GRUNTS )
Surprised you didn 't bring one of your trophies , or medals .
You said it had to be something I cared about , so ...
I brought this .
Lights out .
Okay , so ...
Listen , once we ask for Katie 's return ,
we have to keep these blindfolds on , all right ?
AleeyKat said not to look in his face .
If you do ,
you 're messed up forever .
It 's different for everyone , but it only ends in insanity , or death .
Okay .
Okay , hold my hand , hold my hand . You hold her hand , too , okay ?
We all have to hold hands .
How long do you think we 're gonna give this ?
As long as it takes .
( FOREST QUIETS )
Keep your blindfolds on .
( TWIGS SNAPPING )
( SHUDDERING )
( BELL TOLLS )
Do you hear that ?
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( BELL TOLLS )
Guys , we shouldn 't be doing this .
- She 's right . - It 's too late .
- ( BELL TOLLS ) - ( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( TWIGS SNAPPING )
( TWIGS CONTINUE SNAPPING )
( BREATHING RAPIDLY )
( SCREAMING )
- Chloe ! Chloe ! - Chloe , come back !
- Come on ! Chloe ! - Come back , Chloe !
( PANTING )
( GROANS )
( SCREAMING )
( GASPS )
Chloe ?
Hallie !
( GASPING )
( BOTH SCREAM )
Oh , my God ! Hallie .
- Where 's Chloe ? - I don 't know !
I told her to keep her freaking blindfold on .
- She ... - Chloe !
( BOTH YELP )
- Oh , my God , Chloe ! - Chloe !
Jesus , Chloe , you scared us to death ! Where did you go ?
I lost my shoe .
HALLIE : It 's okay .
What happened ?
- You saw him . - Wren .
Chloe , I told you not to take your blindfold off .
- Did you see him ? - Nothing happened .
I just got scared . Okay ?
Something happened , and she knows it . Something happened back there !
You 're right . We didn 't get Katie back . That 's what happened .
Come on .
WREN : Wait , guys . Wait for me .
( KNOCKING ON DOOR )
LIZZIE : Hal ?
Go away .
Are you okay ?
I 'm fine !
I 'm fine ! Just ... I 'll see you later , okay ?
Just go to sleep . We 'll hang tomorrow , okay ?
( MUSIC PLAYING ON PHONE )
( MUSIC DISTORTING )
( MUSIC STOPS )
( CELL PHONE CHIMES )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( GASPS )
( ELECTRICITY BUZZING )
( CREAKING )
( CHOKING )
( SCREAMING )
( CHURCH BELL TOLLING )
Hey .
What 's up with Chloe ? It 's been a few days .
She 's fine . Just a cold .
( WHISTLE BLOWS )
( PANTING ) Hey , Hallie ! Wait up .
- Hey . - Hey .
How you holding up ? I mean , with Katie and everything .
Um ...
Well , I 'm okay . I ...
Hey , tomorrow 's Friday .
We got the weekend coming up .
I was thinking , maybe we should do something .
- Yeah , sure . - ( RUSTLING )
You want to come over tomorrow night ? To my place ?
Hallie .
Hallie ?
- What ? - Are you okay ?
Yeah , that 's cool . Your place ?
Sure .
I 'll see you later ?
Okay .
( TYPING )
( DOOR CLOSING )
( RUSTLING )
( SIGHS IN RELIEF )
Hallie . Hallie , can you ... Can you hear me ? I ...
( STATIC )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
( THUDDING )
( BANGING )
Hello ?
( BOOKCASES CREAKING )
( YELPING )
Oh , God .
( BELL TOLLING )
( WHIMPERING )
( GROANING )
( WREN SOBBING )
Please ! Please help !
( SCREAMING )
No ! No , no !
No !
Please !
No , no !
( WHIMPERING )
( MUFFLED SCREAMING )
( MUFFLED SHRIEKING )
- LIBRARIAN : Miss , are you all right ? - ( WHIMPERING )
- Are you okay ? - Oh , God .
I 'm sorry .
I 'm sorry . I 'm sorry .
Hey . Are you not getting my texts , or something ?
- Look , Wren , I don 't ... - No , no , no .
Look at me . I found proof . I found the proof . Right ?
Look , look , look , I understand .
I understand now , what AleeyKat was trying to tell me .
It 's proof . Read this . Read this with me .
Okay , it says , " paranormal contact with bioelectric systems
" often results in a symbiotic relationship .
" The effects on host organisms have been well documented and manifest
" in various forms , such as ... "
- Wren . Wren . Calm down . - No , no , no .
Shh . Listen to me . " Personality change , bizarre behavior ,
" mental illness , psychosis , loss of contact with reality ,
" self-mutilation , and suicide .
" And nonspecific dissolution . "
They just disappear .
Has ...
Has anything weird happened to you lately , or strange , or ...
Do not hold out on me .
- Okay , so , I was talking with Tom ... - Tom ?
- What 's wrong with Tom ? - What ? Who gives a shit about Tom , Hal ?
- Just tell me what happened . - Okay .
I thought I saw something in the trees .
It was him .
And , what about Chloe ? Have you talked to her ?
I don 't know . I 've called her house , and her mom keeps telling me she 's sick .
Last time I called , she pretty much flat out told me to stay away .
We need to go there right now .
Wren , there 's nothing we can do , and I have track .
- I can 't just leave . - Track ?
I thought you didn 't care about track anymore .
I thought you cared about Chloe .
( GIRLS GASPING )
Chloe .
Chloe . Wake up .
HALLIE : What the hell was that ?
I don 't know , but I told ...
I knew that she saw his face in the woods , you know ?
I knew that she was lying , too . I knew that .
I don 't want to do this anymore .
Yeah , I don 't , either .
But I 'm stuck in it .
And you are , too . You just don 't realize it yet .
Don 't look at me like that . I 'm not doing a " thing . "
All right .
" All right " ? Yeah , don 't say " All right . "
We only watched the website video .
But Chloe , she saw him in the woods .
- Wren , I can 't keep ... - Read the book that I showed you .
You will see the body count , okay ? Thousands of disappearances .
Search parties , faces on milk cartons . I 'm not making this shit up .
And it all happened exactly like AleeyKat said .
It 's probably some 50-year-old dude living in his parents ' basement ,
getting off on e-mailing teenage girls every day .
Did you ever think of that ? Did you ?
So , you think that you can just go back to real life ?
Yeah , I do . In fact , I have a real-life date
with real-life Tom tonight . In real life .
He 's not gonna stop !
And going on a date with fucking Abercrombie Tom
is not gonna change anything !
You know I 'm right !
You know I 'm right .
- Hey . - Hey .
Sorry I 'm late .
- No worries . Come on in . - Thanks .
I thought I had the wrong house
because there weren 't any cars in the driveway .
Yeah , my dad 's at this business thing , and Mom 's at her book club , so ...
So , nobody 's home ?
No , it 's just us . Is that okay ?
- Yeah ? - Yeah .
I didn 't know you were such a music geek .
Hmm .
( MUSIC PLAYING )
( TOM SIGHS )
So , this is my dad 's , but I like it .
Cool .
Do you want me to put something else on , or ...
- No . This is great . - Okay . Cool .
( MUSIC DISTORTS )
- What ? - Do you hear that ?
- Yeah . It 's good , right ? - ( MUSIC PLAYING NORMALLY )
( RUSTLING )
Hey .
Hey , come here .
( GROWLING )
( SCREAMING )
What the hell ?
Hallie , I didn 't do anything .
I know . Oh , God .
Are you okay ?
Here .
Have you told anyone else about this ?
( SIGHS )
If Katie was on some weird Slender Man website , then
who knows who she met ? I mean ...
Probably some weird guy in a van , you know ?
I hate to say it .
( SIGHS )
Is this it ?
- No , don 't . - ( SCOFFS ) Come on .
Tom , please . You can 't go on that site .
- It 's just a video . - It 's not just a video .
Promise me you won 't ever watch that video .
Tom , I 'm serious . Please promise .
Okay . Okay , I promise .
Really .
I need to go .
All right , first , let 's all take a moment to observe ...
- Tom . Hey . - ... the exterior anatomy here .
Tom ? Tom .
Hey . Are you okay ?
Now , you 'll notice that the cornea looks a little cloudy and bluish .
That happens naturally because of the preservation process .
So , very carefully , with your scalpels ,
I want you to make a slice right through the sclera as evenly as you can .
That 's gonna separate the anterior features of the eye .
KATIE : Hallie .
- Katie ? - Hallie .
Hallie .
Katie ?
Hallie !
- Help me , Hallie . - Katie ?
Katie ?
( ECHOING ) Hallie .
Katie !
Katie , come back !
( GRUNTING ) Katie !
Katie !
KATIE : Hallie , help me .
( GASPS )
( WHIMPERING )
( FOOTSTEPS APPROACHING )
( SCREAMS )
( GROANING )
( COUGHING )
( RETCHING )
( SCREAMING )
- ( GASPS ) - HALLIE 'S DAD : Come on , breathe .
HALLIE 'S MOM : You 're gonna be okay .
- HALLIE 'S DAD : Breathe ... - HALLIE 'S MOM : How long did they say ?
- I don 't know . Come on . Come on . - It 's gonna be okay .
- Just breathe , sweetheart . - Breathe , breathe .
Come on . We got you . We got you . Stay up .
That 's right , deep breath .
- Just breathe . Deep breaths . - Lizzie , what 's going on ?
Oh , my God . Lizzie !
- The ambulance is on its way . - Lizzie .
Lizzie , it 's okay . Just look at me .
- We got you . - It 's okay , baby , it 's okay .
Okay , the ambulance is on its way , honey .
No . No , Lizzie !
- Lizzie , wake up ! Lizzie ! - We 're all here , Lizzie .
- Dad , do something ! - Where is that ambulance ?
- I 'm doing my best . Come on , Lizzie ! - Lizzie , wake up !
- Come on , Lizzie , just breathe . - Lizzie , wake up !
( HEART MONITOR BEEPING )
- ( DOOR OPENS ) - ( HALLIE 'S DAD EXHALES )
Blood tests are negative . She 's gonna be fine .
They think it was just some kind of panic attack .
They want to keep her to monitor her for at least another day .
( ALL LAUGHING )
( LAUGHING EVILLY )
No . No .
Lizzie ? Lizzie ? ( SOBBING )
Lizzie ! Lizzie !
Lizzie !
Lizzie , please .
Lizzie ?
( GROANING )
HALLIE 'S MOM : Hallie ?
Hallie ?
Hallie , are you okay ?
What 's the matter ?
HALLIE 'S DAD : Sweetheart , what 's going on ?
Hey . She 's okay . She 's okay .
It 's all right . She 's gonna be fine .
( PHONE RINGING )
NURSE : ( ON PA ) Dr. Barnes , 4721 . Dr. Barnes , 4721 .
( LIZZIE SHRIEKING )
- BP 80 / 40 . - Let 's get her moving .
- Lizzie ! - Get her moving .
- Lizzie ! - Let 's get her moving .
- Where are they taking her ? - I 've got to get her to the ICU .
- Lizzie ! - He had no face .
( GROANING ) He had no face ! He had no face !
He had no face !
( SOBBING ) Lizzie !
Okay . So , now , what do I do ?
Just sacrifice something you love .
Wren !
Damn it , Wren ! I know you 're in there !
Open up !
Wren !
( WINDOW CREAKING )
( WIND HOWLING )
( BREATHING HEAVILY )
Wren , what are you doing ?
Wren , take my hand . Come on .
Wren , you 're gonna fall ! Wren .
- Wren ! - ( YELPS )
( WREN CRYING )
I 'm sorry .
You 're sorry ? That 's it ? That 's my sister ! Why would you do that ?
She came to me .
- Wren , she 's in the hospital ! - She came to me .
It was before I knew .
To get Lizzie back , to make him stop ,
you can 't just give him something you love .
It 's not enough .
He wants us !
He wants us ! ( SOBBING )
( CREATURE TRILLING )
( CELL PHONE BUZZING )
( GASPS )
Hello ?
- ( STATIC ) - ( GASPS )
WREN : No .
That 's here . That 's here .
- ( SOBBING ) - ( TRILLING CONTINUES )
Wait , wait , Hallie !
No .
( TRILLING INTENSIFIES )
( GIRLS WHIMPERING )
( BOTH SCREAM )
Wren ! Wren !
WREN : To get Lizzie back ...
He had no face !
... to make him stop ...
Hallie , are you okay ?
... you can 't just give him something you love .
He wants us !
( BELL TOLLS )
( INSECTS BUZZING )
( TWIGS SNAPPING )
( CREAKING )
( SCREAMS )
Take me .
( SCREAMING )
( PANTING )
( GASPS )
( CREAKING )
( SCREAMING )
( HEART BEATING )
HALLIE : Lizzie !
( HEART MONITOR BEEPING )
Hallie ! No !
Hallie ! Hallie ! No !
- Honey ! It 's okay ! - Hallie ! No ! No !
It 's okay .
- Nurse ! Somebody help us ! - Hallie ! Hallie !
- Hallie ! - Can we get a nurse in here ?
No ! No ! No !
Right here .
Hallie ! No !
LIZZIE : Hallie , Katie , Chloe , Wren .
There 's almost always a pattern .
He only shows himself just enough to infect us .
The more fear he creates , the more fascinated we get .
We talk and write about him , share pictures , click on links ,
Photoshop images . That 's how a virus works .
That 's how it spreads .
And some people cross the line and actually seek him out ,
like my sister and her friends did .
And those messed-up people go out and do messed-up things
that become more stories for people to tell .
It 's all spreading his word . You know ?
( STUDENTS CHATTERING )
Subtitles by explosiveskull Resync by GoldenBeard
MAN 1 : We know he abducts people .
MAN 2 : I started getting a ringing in my ears .
( SPEAKING OTHER LANGUAGE )
( SPEAKING FRENCH )
MAN 3 : It 's the thing that we fear .
MAN 4 : There 'd been reports of strange lights coming from the woods .
MAN 5 : Viral nature of his ever-expanding reach and influence .
I keep having nightmares about his pale face .
REPORTER : Pictures include variations of a thin man with a blanked-out face .
MAN 6 : He seduces them .